Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Audio
  - Interview with Steve Doughton (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), April 20, 1994
    - Original audio recording, ID 221.0262 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0262)
    - Access CDs (Box 168, Cd 221.0539, Cd 221.0541)
  - Interview with Julie Hair (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), April 27, 1994
    - Tape 1 -- Part 1 and 2
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0263 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0263)
      - Access CDs (Box 168, Cd 221.0543, Cd 221.0545)
    - Tape 2
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0264 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0264)
      - Access CD (Box 168, Cd 221.0547)
  - Interview with Kiki Smith (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), April 28, 1994
    - Tape 1 -- Part 1 and 2
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0259 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0259)
      - Access CDs (Box 168, Cd 221.0529, Cd 221.0531)
    - Tape 2
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0260 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0260)
        Duration: 7 minutes
      - Access CD (Box 168, Cd 221.0533)
  - Interview with Nancy Spero, May 26, 1995
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0246 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0246)
    - Tape 2, Panel reject How to Shoot, ID 221.0247 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0247)
  - Interview with Kiki Smith (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), June 6, 1995
    - Original audio recording, ID 221.0258 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0258)
    - Access CDs (Box 168, Cd 221.0525, Cd 221.0527)
  - Interview with Julia Kristeva, July 31, 1995; ID 221.0241 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0241)
  - Todd Alden, Collector's Shit, May 1, 1996
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0265 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0265)
    - Tape 2 -- Copy, ID 221.0266 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0266)
  - Interviews with Michael Cohen (Aug 22) and Victor Estrada (Aug 23), August 22-23, 1996; ID 221.0255 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0255)
  - "Baudrillard on Artaud", Jean Baudrillard at The Drawing Center, November 20, 1996; ID 221.0267 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0267)
  - LA: Narcotics Anonymous, December 12, 1996; ID 221.0254 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0254)
  - Interview with Paul Virilio, Pure War, December 26, 1996; ID 221.0243 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0243)
  - Chance Event audio, 1996
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0231 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0231)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0232 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0232)
    - Tape 3, ID 221.0233 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0233)
    - Tape 4, ID 221.0234 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0234)
    - Tape 5, ID 221.0235 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0235)
    - Tape 6, ID 221.0236 (Box 86, Dat ID 221.0236)
    - Tape 7, ID 221.0237 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0237)
    - Tape 8, ID 221.0238 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0238)
    - Tape 9, ID 221.0239 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0239)
    - Tape 10, ID 221.0240 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0240)
  - Chance Event -- "Suicide Moi" Jean Baudrillard and the Chance band, 1996; ID 221.0423 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0423)
  - Interview with Jane Dikson, January 29, 1997; ID 221.0248 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0248)
  - S.L. / Bob Dobbs May 1997, ID 221.0443 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0443)
  - Violent Femmes audio, circa 1998; ID 221.0230 (Box 85, Media ID 221.0230)
    Original Format: Digital Audio
  - Ilana [Levy], Paris, May 6, 2001; ID 221.0271 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0271)
  - Guila, May 19, 2001; ID 221.0273 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0273)
  - Guila (May 19) and Shosh (May 21), May 19 and 21, 2001; ID 221.0274 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0274)
  - Shosh, May 21, 2001; ID 221.0275 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0275)
  - Marcel Wolfmann, 2nd session with Yvonne, December 1, 2002; ID 221.0270 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0270)
  - Artaud, Art Center, June 5, 2003; ID 221.0268 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0268)
  - Artaud, Derrida, etc., Art Center, June 19, 2003; ID 221.0269 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0269)
  - The Carlin Case, Pacifica Radio Archive, undated; ID 221.0277 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0277)
    This recording includes interviews with Gorman, Farrell, Ginsberg, Burroughs, Doctorow, Krasnow, Cowan, Moody, Johnson, and Wiley.
  - "Beatbox" (Plush 03), undated; ID 221.0313 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0313)
  - Bill Morrrissey / Captain Beefheart, undated; ID 221.0294 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0294)
  - Chris Kraus, undated; ID 221.0244 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0244)
  - The Collected Interviews of W. Burroughs, undated; ID 221.0316 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0316)
  - Culture Club / Stevie Ray Vaughn / Cash / [Burnette], undated; ID 221.0284 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0284)
  - Daniel F., undated; ID 221.0253 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0253)
  - David, undated
    - Original audio recording, ID 221.0323 (Box 90, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0323)
    - Access CD (Box 167, Cd 221.0453)
  - David Nikias "The English Channel", undated; ID 221.0444 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0444)
  - Epson Update, undated; ID 221.0317 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0317)
  - Foucault, Fearless Speech, undated; ID 221.0315 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0315)
  - Friends of Dean Martinez, undated; ID 221.0276 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0276)
  - Gary Lucas / Evangeline, undated; ID 221.0293 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0293)
  - Homage to Erik Satie, undated
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0371 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0371)
      Format: LP
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0370 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0370)
  - Homer, undated
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0281 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0281)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0282 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0282)
  - Interview with Andres Serrano, undated; ID 221.0245
    - Original audio recording (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0245)
    - Access CDs (Box Shared Fales 144, Cd 221.0245_pt.1, 221.0245_pt.2)
  - Interview with Ken Jordan, undated; ID 221.0249 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0249)
  - Jeff Koons, undated; ID 221.0314 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0314)
  - Joe Johnson "Radio", undated; ID 221.0445 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0445)
  - John Giorno and Anne Waldman, undated
    - Tape 1 -- Giorno, ID 221.0367 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0367)
    - Tape 2 -- Waldman, ID 221.0368 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0368)
  - Joy Division, undated; ID 221.0283 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0283)
  - Leisure Units, undated; ID 221.0286 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0286)
  - Lotringer / Kelley interview, undated; ID 221.0242 (Box 86, Audiocassette ID 221.0242)
  - Mazzy Star / Patsy Cline, undated; ID 221.0287 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0287)
  - Michael Row the Boat Ashore, undated; ID 221.0280 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0280)
  - Music for all seasons, undated; ID 221.0291 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0291)
  - Music of the Crusades, 13th Century, undated; ID 221.0285 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0285)
  - Native Agents: Chris Kraus "Aliens and Anorexia", undated; ID 221.0424 (Box 91, Audiocassette ID 221.0424)
    Duration: 2 minutes
  - Nick's Memorial, undated
    - Reel 1
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0224 (Box 90, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0224)
      - Access CD (Box 167, Cd 221.0451)
    - Reel 2
      - Original audio recording, ID 221.0225 (Box 90, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0225)
      - Access CD (Box 167, Cd 221.0452)
  - Patsy Cline / [indecipherable], undated; ID 221.0288 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0288)
  - "PianoBook" (Plush 06), undated; ID 221.0312 (Box 88, Cd ID 221.0312)
  - Poulenc Plays Poulenc and Satie, undated; ID 221.0369 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0369)
  - Puppet Show Overdub, undated
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0278 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0278)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0279 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0279)
  - "Rabelais", text by S. Lotringer, read by Daniel Ivernel, undated; ID 221.0227 (Box 85, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0227)
  - Slayer, undated; ID 221.0292 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0292)
  - Unknown audiotapes, undated
    - Reel 1, ID 221.0228 (Box 85, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0228)
    - Reel 2, ID 221.0229 (Box 85, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0229)
    - Reel 3, ID 221.0296 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0296)
    - Reel 4, ID 221.0297 (Box 87, Audiocassette ID 221.0297)
    - Reel 5, 221.0299 (Box 87, Half inch audio reel 221.0299)
    - Reel 6, ID 221.0300 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0300)
    - Reel 7, ID 221.0301 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0301)
    - Reel 8, ID 221.0302 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0302)
    - Reel 9, ID 221.0303 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0303)
    - Reel 10, ID 221.0304 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0304)
    - Reel 11, ID 221.0305 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0305)
    - Reel 12, ID 221.0306 (Box 87, Quarter inch audio reel ID 221.0306)
  - Voodoo Trance Music, Ritual Drums of Haiti, undated; ID 221.0372 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0372)
  - William S. Burroughs / John Giorno
    - Tape 1 -- Burroughs, ID 221.0365 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0365)
    - Tape 2 -- Giorno, ID 221.0366 (Box 89, Media ID 221.0366)
- Series XII: Film
  Series XII: Film is arranged alphabetically.
  - The Golden Bowl, or, Repression, 1984-1989
    - Workprint, circa 1984-1986; ID 221.0179 (Reel 221.0179, 16mm film reels 221.0179)
    - Titles and Credits, 1989; ID 221.0180 (Reel 221.0180, 16mm film reels 221.0180)
  - Kind Shot -- A True Story, undated; ID 221.0184 (Reel 221.0184, 16mm film reels 221.0184)
  - Outtakes, undated
    - "Cool; Arrival + Eating / [biass] love", ID 221.0183 (Reel 221.0183, 16mm film reels 221.0183)
    - "Hot; All fine cut, gray car", ID 221.0181 (Reel 221.0181, 16mm film reels 221.0181)
    - "Worm; L. Ann + [lows], bun + Barn, George + Phone", ID 221.0182 (Reel 221.0182, 16mm film reels 221.0182)
  - Print I, undated; ID 221.0186 (Case 221.0186, 16mm film reels 221.0186)
  - Too Sensitive to Touch, circa 1981
    - 16mm film, ID 221.0178 (Reel 221.0178, 16mm film reels 221.0178)
    - Revised Version, ID 221.0177 (Reel 221.0177, 16mm film reels 221.0177)
  - Workprint B, undated; ID 221.0185 (Case 221.0185, Super 8mm film reel 221.0185)
  - Unlabeled film reels, undated
    - Reel 1, ID 221.0187 (Reel 221.0187, 16mm film reels 221.0187)
    - Reel 2, ID 221.0188 (Reel 221.0188, 16mm film reels 221.0188)
    - Reel 3, ID 221.0189 (Reel 221.0189, 16mm film reels 221.0189)
  - Unlabeled film fragments, assorted, undated; ID 221.0190 (Case 221.0190, Super 8mm film reel 221.0190)
- Series XIII: Computer Disks
  - Subseries A: Access Copies - Computer Disks
  - Subseries B: Originals - Computer Disks
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #1, ID 221.0001 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0001)
      Format: 3.5 in. diskette
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #2, ID 221.0002 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0002)
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #3, ID 221.0003 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0003)
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #4, ID 221.0004 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0004)
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #5, ID 221.0005 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0005)
    - David Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #6, ID 221.0006 (Box 71, Media ID 221.0006)
    - Lotringer Hard Disk Portable, ID 221.0318 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0318)
      Format: CD-R
    - Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #7, ID 221.0319 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0319)
    - Wojnarowicz 3.5 in. Diskette #8, ID 221.032 (Box 88, Media ID 221.032)
    - 3.5 in. diskette, file: derrida, ID 221.0321 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0321)
    - 3.5 in. mixed diskette, ID 221.0322 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0322)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Tea Book, ID 221.0324 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0324)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Cixous Interview, ID 221.0325 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0325)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Dennie Del Zotto resume + photographs / portfolio, ID 221.0326 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0326)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Interview: John Cage, ID 221.0327 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0327)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Anthropophagy, ID 221.0328 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0328)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Chris Summer 92, ID 221.0329 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0329)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Semiotext(e), ID 221.0330 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0330)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Dick 2, ID 221.0331 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0331)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: PW mss files, ID 221.0332 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0332)
    - 3.5 in. diskette: Guattari/ Uno by Remi, ID 221.0333 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0333)
    - 5 in. diskette: Kathy Acker Interviews #1, ID 221.0334 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0334)
      Format: 5 in. diskette
    - 5 in. diskette: Kathy Acker Interviews #2, ID 221.0335 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0335)
    - 5 in. diskette: Kathy Acker Interviews #3, ID 221.0336 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0336)
    - 5 in. diskette: Kathy Acker Interviews #4, ID 221.0337 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0337)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foucault #1, ID 221.0338 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0338)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foucault #2, ID 221.0339 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0339)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foucault #3, ID 221.0340 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0340)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foucault #4, ID 221.0341 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0341)
    - 5 in. diskette: Baudrillard, ID 221.0342 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0342)
    - 5 in. diskette: Jim Fleming: Subscribers Semio, ID 221.0343 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0343)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foreign Agent (1) On sexual[ity] (2) Death, ID 221.0344 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0344)
    - 5 in. diskette: Prints 1, ID 221.0345 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0345)
    - 5 in. diskette: Prints 2, ID 221.0346 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0346)
    - 5 in. diskette: Word Perfect 4.1, ID 221.0347 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0347)
    - 5 in. diskette: PC-Write Workdisk #1, ID 221.0348 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0348)
    - 5 in. diskette: PC-Write Workdisk #2, ID 221.0349 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0349)
    - 5 in. diskette: PC-Write Workdisk #3, ID 221.0350 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0350)
    - 5 in. diskette: PC-Write Workdisk #4, ID 221.0351 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0351)
    - 5 in. diskette: PC-Write Workdisk #5, ID 221.0352 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0352)
    - 5 in. diskette: Foucault #5, ID 221.0353 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0353)
    - 5 in. diskette: Dachau (Listen to Me), ID 221.0354 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0354)
    - 5 in. diskette: Hitler #1, ID 221.0355 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0355)
    - 5 in. diskette: Hitler #2, ID 221.0356 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0356)
    - 5 in. diskette: Hitler #3, ID 221.0357 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0357)
    - 5 in. diskette: PW #1, ID 221.0358 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0358)
    - 5 in. diskette: PW #2, ID 221.0359 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0359)
    - 5 in. diskette: Cahier 1, ID 221.0360 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0360)
    - 5 in. diskette: MS-DOS Backup, ID 221.0361 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0361)
    - 5 in. diskette: MS-DOS Operating System, ID 221.0362 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0362)
    - Zip drive: Semiotext(e) - Virilio, ID 221.0363 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0363)
      Format: Zip drive
    - Zip drive: Flesh-Eating Technologies, ID 221.0364 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0364)
    - 3.5" diskette: J [Rancier], Deleuze and Aesthetics, undated; ID 221.0427 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0427)
    - CD: Sylvere Photos, Paris March 10-14 2007 (Baudrillard's funeral + visit with S. family), ID 221.0428 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0428)
    - 5" diskette: Foucault, undated; ID 221.0429 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0429)
    - 5" diskette: Foucault (back up), undated; ID 221.0430 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0430)
    - 5" diskette: Artaud Play, undated; ID 221.0431 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0431)
    - 5" diskette: Artaud Play (back up), undated; ID 221.0432 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0432)
    - 5" diskette: Artaud Play (back up), undated; ID 221.0433 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0433)
    - 3.5" diskette: Native Agents: Deran Ludd "Sick Burn Cut" text (word4), maps (Aldus FreeHand), 1991; ID 221.0434 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0434)
    - 3.5" diskette: Unsolicited submissions Sebastian Job "Gyrandromorphic" (9 files microsoft word4, macintosh formatted), undated; ID 221.0435 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0435)
    - 3.5" diskette: Anthology "More & Less" text Carol Irving "Art criticism + memo for Chris", 1996; ID 221.0436 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0436)
    - 3.5" diskette: "Credits D, interview, liner, lyrics, CD {cal baby}", undated; ID 221.0437 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0437)
    - 5" diskette: Native Agents Lynne Tillman "Madame Realism Complex", undated; ID 221.0438 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0438)
    - 5" diskette: Native Agents Lynne Tillman "Madame Realism Complex", 1992; ID 221.0439 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0439)
    - 3.5" diskette: Dobbs, undated; ID 221.0440 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0440)
    - 3.5" diskette: "Has resource fork PHATIC COMMUNION", undated; ID 221.0441 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0441)
    - CD: Annie Shelton "Erewhon" Ramp Nov 2002, ID 221.0442 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0442)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Individuals
    - Pat, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - [Sandlin, David], 1997 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Flyers, Press Releases and Mass-mailouts
    - posters, undated (Box 96, Folder 1)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Semiotext(e) Projects
  - Subseries A: Issues and Conferences
    - Conference "The Two Saussures": Flyer Printing Plate, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Cover Layout, c. 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Cover Design, c. 1978 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Proofs (first), 1978 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Documents, c. 1980 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Layouts, c. 1980 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents, c. 1980 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents, c. 1980 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents 'Lotta Continua", 1979 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents 'Lotta Continua", 1979 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Visual Materials, c. 1980 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Issue 10 "Polysexuality": Cover Design, Color Separation [?], c. 1980 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Event "Polysexuality" at the Kitchen: Flyers, c. 1981 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Cover Layout, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - (unpublished) "Australasia Issue": Proposal, c. 1993 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Cover Designs, c. 1995 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Documents, c. 1995 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Conferences "Deleuze (Guattari On the Edge)", 1999 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Visual Material, 1990s (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - (unpublished) "Flesh-Eating Technologies Issue": Visual Material, 2000s (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Unknown Issue: Layouts, undated (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Unknown Issue: Visual Source Material and Layouts, undated (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Event "Nova Convention" Poster, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys" layouts, c. 1980 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Event "Cemnot3kct" - Poster, c. 1984 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Event "Chance" poster, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Foreign, Native and Active Agents Book Series
    - Foreign Agents: Unpublished Deleuze Anthology: Texts, 1990s (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Native Agents: "William Burroughs Live": Texts, c. 2000 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Native Agents: "David Wojnarowicz": Press, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - Terence Costello (various mss), 1970s (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Unknown author "The Epidog", undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Subject Files
  - British Rock Lives: Village Voice - March 28, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - I Contact: contact with the lives of Patti Smith, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Punk #17, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Avant-Punk: Village Voice Special Edition, October 24, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Paranoids Anonymous Newsletter #1: Tillman, Lynne, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - La Quinzaine Litteraire: 376 August 1982 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Grundberg, Andy (1), Jonathan (2), Laibaros, Joni (1), Mosher, P. (Charlemagne Palestine - 2), various (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - "Dear Charlotte, 1968 is over..." Kathy Acker poster, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 9a)
  - "Ashtray" poster, 1991 (Folder 19)
  - "Antonin Artaud" poster, undated (Folder 19)
  - Biographical chronology of Simone Adolphine Weil (Roll-storage oversized roll)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Sylvere Lotringer Projects
  - Subseries A: Writing
    - The New York Times Magazine, July 3, 1977, section 6, "A New Vision of Dreams: Insights from Sleep Research" (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Impulse - Death Issue - printed plastic bags (promo), 1985 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Photostats (negatives) of Sylvere's articles in Les Lettres françaises (Folder 1 Right)
  - Subseries B: Film
    - Film "How to Shoot a Crime" poster, undated (Box 109)
  - Subseries C: Conferences, Events and Tours
    - Antonin Artaud Events at the Drawing Centre - poster, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - "The Obesity of Art", undated (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - "Simone Weil" at Columbia - poster with poster design, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Columbia University Record, November 12, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - "French Theory in America", 1997 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - "Kafka Colloque", 1989 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - "The Third Wave: Art and French Theory", undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Photographic Materials
  - Subseries A: Professional
    - Pino Guiseppe (Andy Braxton -2, Unknown Subject -1); Volz, Wolfgang (Christo -1); Watier (2); (S. Lotringer -3); (Deran Ludd - 1); (Unknown Subject -1) (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - unidentified portraits of a woman, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
- OVERSIZE Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies
  - Les Lettres Francaise, various (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - "Le Monde", 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1979 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Paris Lettres & Student (Edinburgh), 1959-1960 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Allan, Blaine "Nicholas Ray", undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - clippings: Simone Weil, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
- OVERSIZE Series IX: Copies of Publications
  - Subseries A: Semiotext(e) Issues
    - Semiotext(e) Architecture, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Special Issue: "Loving Boys", 1980 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Sylvere Lotringer's Publications
    - Impulse Death Issue, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Interview with Artaud's Doctor in Impulse, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - S.L. Interview in Paper, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Interview with Jane Dickson in Bomb, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Archived website, November 2017- ongoing; Semiotexte; 3 websites in 1 collection of archived websites.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued annually.
  Appraisal
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored with the permission of the content owner. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.autonomedia.org/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.